Finding Aid for the Van Bogert Papers PASC.0153
UCLA Library Special Collections
Van Bogert papers
1955-1956
UCLA Library Special Collections
Bogert, Van
PASC.0153
8.0 Linear Feet (20 boxes)
At the time the finding aid was created, there was no biographical information available about Van BogertThe collection consists of various drafts of scripts, production material, photographs, art work, and music from several television and motion picture productions.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Connie McGuigan, 1981.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 997094163606533
Biography
At the time the finding aid was created, there was no biographical information available about Van Bogert.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of Van Bogert. The bulk of the collection includes drafts of scripts for several television and motion picture productions. Includes televison scripts representing the series The Affairs of China Smith, Broken Arrow, My Friend Flicka, The 20th Century-Fox Hour, and You Are There. The motion pictures projects represent the films Carousel, Can, Can, Daddy Long Legs, The King and I, and The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit, among others. Additionally there is a small amount of production material, black and white photographs, art work, and music.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Motion Picture Projects
Television Projects
Television production and direction -- Archives.; Motion picture producers and directors -- Archives.; Television writers -- Archives.; Bogert, Van--Archives.
- Motion Picture Projects
  - x
    - D-DAY, THE SIXTH OF JUNE (1956) (Box 17, Folder 7)
      General note
      Black and white photograph of hair styles and make-up of Robert Taylor, Dana Wynter, George Pelling, Jennifer Raine, Louise Arthur, Marie Brown and Marie Todd, with one negative of Richard Todd.
    - D-DAY, THE SIXTH OF JUNE (1956) (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Written by Harry Brown. First draft 8/17/55, Revised draft continuity by Harry Brown and Ivan Moffat 10/6/55.
    - D-DAY, THE SIXTH OF JUNE (1956) (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Revised final script 12/16/55.
    - D-DAY, THE SIXTH OF JUNE (1956) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Black and white photographs (122) and negative (1) of wardrobe, hair styles and make-up of Robert Taylor, Dana Wynter, George Pelling, Jennifer Raine, Louise Arthur, Marie Brown, Richard Todd, and minor character
    - EGYPTIAN, THE (1954) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Photocopies of artist renderings of costumes for the Egyptian. Characters: Merit, Denmut, Baketamon, Nefer, Kipa, Horemheb, Eie, Akhnaton, and Sinhue, with 5 sheets of storyboards, pencil drawn.
    - GIRL CAN'T HELP IT (1956) (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Written by Frank Tashlin. First draft 8/10/56.
    - GIRL IN THE RED VELVET SWING, THE (1955) (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Written by Charles Brackett and Walter Reisch. Working script 2/4/55, First draft continuity 2/25/55, includes, break down list of actors and dancers for dance sequences.
    - GIRL IN THE RED VELVET SWING, THE (1955) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Cast list.
    - GOOD MORNING MISS DOVE (1955) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Staff list.
    - GOODMORNING MISS DOVE (1955) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Written by Eleanore Griffin. First draft continuity 5/13/55, Temporary script 6/27/55 bound with breakdown.
    - HILDA CRANE (1956) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Written by Philip Dunne. Working script 11/10/55, Final script 12/20/55.
    - HOW TO BE VERY, VERY POPULAR (1955) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - HOW TO BE VERY, VERY POPULAR (1955) (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Written by Nunnally Johnson. Final script 1/11/55.
    - KING AND I, THE (1956) (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Black and white photographs (5).
    - KING AND I, THE (1956) (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Written by Ernest Lehamn. First draft 11/30/54, Revised final 10/04/55.
    - LAST WAGON, THE (1956) (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Written by James Edward Grant. Revised final 1/27/56.
    - LEFT HAND OF GOD, THE (1955) (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Written by Alfred Hayes. 2/22/55.
    - LIEUTENANT WORE SKIRTS, THE (1956) (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Entitled The Camp Follower written by Albert Beich. First draft written 7/2/53, Working script, written by Frank Tashlin 6/1/55.
    - LIEUTENANT WORE SKIRTS, THE (1956) (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Entitled The Retread written by Frank Tashlin. Revised first draft continuity (incomplete through page 30, sequence 34), n.d., Temporary 7/18/55.
    - LIEUTENANT WORE SKIRTS, THE (1956) (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Entitled I Lost my Wife to the Army written by Frank Tashlin. Final script 8/12/55.
    - LORD VANITY (UNPRODUCED) (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Art department layouts of sets, revised final script 8/26/64.
    - LOVE IS A MANY SPLENDORED THING (1955) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Cast and staff list, publicity personnel addresses.
    - LOVE IS A MANY SPLENDORED THING (1955) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Black and white photographs and negatives (5) of Chungking sequence.
    - LOVE IS A MANY SPLENDORED THING (1955) (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Black and white photographs (15) of hair styles, wardrobe shots, includes Leonard Strong, Richard Loo, Murray Matheson, Bill Holder, Torin Thatcher and Kam Tong.
    - LOVE IS A MANY SPLENDORED THING (1955) (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Black and white photographs (14) and negatives (6) of interior Queen Elizabeth Hospital, Hong Kong.
    - LOVE IS A MANY SPLENDORED THING (1955) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Black and white photographs (27) and negs.(3) of restaurant boat, research department photocopies of Tai Pak Floating Restaurant in Hong Kong.
    - LOVE IS A MANY SPLENDORED THING (1955) (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Black and white photographs (37) of hair styles, wardrobe includes Donna Martall, Jorja Courtright, Candice Lee, Sue Young, Isubel Elsom, and Virginia Gregg, with 7 wardrobe photographs.
    - MAN IN THE GRAY FLANNEL SUIT, THE (1956) (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Written by Nunnally Johnson. Incomplete script 9/22/55.
    - MAN WHO NEVER WAS, THE (1956) (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Written by Simon Wincelberg. Temporary script 1/3/55, Final script 1/14/55.
    - OH, MEN! OH, WOMEN! (1957) (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Written by Nunnally Johnson. First draft script 4/30/56.
    - ON THE THERESHOLD OF SPACE (1956) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - ON THE THRESHOLD OF SPACE (1956) (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Written by Simon Wincelberg. Final script 08/29/55, Revised final 08/05/55.
    - ON THE THRESHOLD OF SPACE (1956) (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Entitled Windblast written by Simon Wincelberg. Final Script 7/5/55, Revised final 8/5/55.
    - ON THE THRESHOLD OF SPACE (1956) (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Entitled Space Medicine written by Simon Wincelberg. Revised first draft 6/8/55.
    - OX-BOW INCIDENT, THE (1943) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Staff and crew list.
    - PROUD ONES, THE (1956) (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Written by Joseph Petracca & Edmund H. North. First draft n.d., final draft 7/14/55, Revised final 09/19/55, Shooting final 10/25/55, Revised shooting final 12/5/55.
    - RAINS CAME, THE (1959) (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Written by Merle Miller. 2/24/55
    - REVOLT OF MAMIE STOVER,THE (1956) (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Written by Sydney Boehm. Revised Final 1/20/55, Shooting final 10/31/55.
    - RUN OF THE ARROW (1952) (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Written by Samuel Fuller, Treatment 12/31/52.
    - SEVEN CITIES OF GOLD (1956) (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Written by Richard L. Breen & Joseph Petracca. Revised shooting final script 2/21/55.
    - SHE-DEVIL, THE (1956) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - TALL MEN, THE (1955) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Staff and crew list, Mexico location, total expenditures.
    - TALL MEN, THE (1955) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Written by Frank Nugent and Sydney Boehm. Final Script 02/25/55.
    - TEENAGE REBEL (1956) (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Written by Charles Brackett and Walter Reisch. First draft continuity 4/18/56.
    - TEENAGE REBEL (1956) (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Entitled A Roomful of Roses written by Charles Brackett and Walter Reisch. Working script 3/8/56.
    - THERE'S NO BUSINESS LIKE SHOW BUSINESS (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Written by Phoebe and Henry Ephron. Shooting final script 4/26/54, Revised shooting script 5/12/54.
    - THREE BRAVE MEN (1957) (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Written by Philip Dunne. Revised final script 8/25/56.
    - TRUE STORY OF JESSE JAMES (1957) (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Written by Walter Newman. Temporary script 09/04/56.
    - UNIDENTIFIED PROJECT(S) (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Includes wardrobe, hair styles, Chicquita the champanzee. Group shots of unidentifed cowboy on horse back, man out doors, one mounted photograph of women 1930's.
    - VIEW FROM POMPEY'S HEAD, THE (1955) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Studio staff, crew, and cast list.
    - VIRGIN QUEEN, THE (1956) (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Entitled Sir Walter Raleigh, The Hawk and the Vulture written by Harry Brown. Rev. shooting final 2/17/54, 4th Rev. shooting final 1/27/55, 5th Rev. shooting final 2/21/55.
    - WAYWARD BUS, THE (1957) (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Written by Ivan Moffat. First draft continuity 6/6/56.
  - 23 PACES TO BAKER STREET (1956) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Written by Nigel Balchin. Final script 8/24/55.
  - BERNARDINE (1957) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Written by Theodore Reeves. Working script 3/21/56.
  - BEST THINGS IN LIFE ARE FREE, THE (1956) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Black and white photographs (233) and negatives (18) of wardrobe and hair styles for Sheree North, Julie Van Zandt, Mary Rodman, and minor female roles.
  - BEST THINGS IN LIFE ARE FREE, THE (1956) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Production material: casting vouchers, group payroll records, employee closing notices, lists of production numbers, requistitions for extra talent, with script, dated April 23, 1956.
  - BEST THINGS IN LIFE ARE FREE, THE (1956) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Black and white photographs (126) of wardrobe and hair styles of Phillis Avery and minor characters.
  - BEST THINGS IN LIFE ARE FREE, THE (1956) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Black and white photographs (110) and negatives (64) of wardrobe and headshots of Gordon MacRae, Ernest Borgnine, Dan Dailey and minor male roles.
  - BEST THINGS IN LIFE ARE FREE, THE (1956) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Written by William Bowers & John Monks Jr. Revised first draft continuity 11/29/55. Revised final script 4/18/56.
  - BETWEEN HEAVEN AND HELL (1956) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Entitled The Day the Century Ended written by Harry Brown. First draft 9/1/55, Revised Final 10/6/55, Revised shooting final 11/25/55.
  - BIGGER THAN LIFE (1956) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Entitled One in a Million written by Cyril Hume & Richard Maibaum. Final script 4/3/56.
  - BIGGER THAN LIFE (1956) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Entitled Ten Feet Tall written Cyril Hume and Richard Maibaum. First draft 12/23/55, Temporary script 1/17/56, Revised temporary script 2/13/56.
  - BOTTOM OF THE BOTTLE, THE (1956) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Written by Sydney Boehm. Writers working script 6/16/55, Revised first draft continuity 7/5/55.
  - BOY ON A DOLPHIN (1957) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Written by Alec Coppel. Working script 8/8/55, Temporary script 9/26/55, Revised script by Richard L. Breen and Walter Reisch 8/21/56.
  - BUS STOP (1956) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Written by George Axelrod. First draft 1/9/56.
  - CAN-CAN (1960) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Written by Claude Binyon. First draft continunity 3/27/56.
  - CAROUSEL (1956) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Scores for musical numbers: Blow High, Blow Low, If I Loved You, You'll never Walk Alone, Mister Snow, June is Bustin' out all Over, When the Children are Asleep, and 4 spirituals.
  - CAROUSEL (1956) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Written by Phoebe and Henry Ephron. Final shooting script 7/14/55 includes production material, cast list, weather outlook, inter-office memos.
  - CAROUSEL (1956) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Production material: staff,cast, studio and location lists.
  - CAROUSEL (1956) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Entitled R-H Project written by Phoebe and Henry Ephron, Final script 06/13/55.
  - DADDY LONG LEGS (1955) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Written by Phoebe and Henry Ephron. Shooting final script 9/29/54.
  - D-DAY, THE SIXTH OF JUNE (1956) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Production material: requistitions for artists, employee closing notices, cast requirements schedule, stunt persons, cast list,staff and crew list, list of arsenal requirements, military props, Navy.
- Television Projects
  - 20th Century-Fox Hour
    - Anastasia (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Written by Bob Eisenbach. Segment only with call sheets and productin report 8/10/55.
    - Between Heaven and Hell (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Written by Bob Eisenbach. First script covers seq. 1-13, 7/6/56, Second script covers seq.32-53, 10/17/56, contains call sheets and daily production reports.
    - Broken Arrow (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Written by Clark E. Reynolds. Final script 2/15/56, bound with narration script, stock shot list, rev. breakdown call sheets, casting voucher requistion for extras, cast list dressing.
    - Bull Whip (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Written by Clark E. Reynolds. First draft Continuity 11/16/56.
    - Calvalcade (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Written by Noel Coward. Adapted by Alistair Cooke, television play by Peter Packer. First draft 8/29/55, Final draft 9/1/55.
    - Cavalcade photographs of Lord and Taylor's Shoe department, caricature from Haprer's Weekly 1866 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Child of the Regiment (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Written by Dewitt Bodeen. Shooting final 7/6/56, bound with revised pages.
    - Christopher Bean (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Written by Mel Dinelli. Final script 10/13/55, Revised final 10/17/55.
    - Courageous Coward (The) (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Written by William Spier. First draft 1/9/56. Final script 1/14/56.
    - Crack Up (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Written by Peter Packer. Final script 12/27/55.
    - Deep Water (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Written by Oscar Millard. Unrevised final 12/5/56.
    - Empty Room (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Written by Dale and Katherine Eunson. Final draft 12/12/55, Shooting final 12/14/55.
    - False Witness (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Written by Ben Feiner. Revised final 7/23/56, breakdowns for stock shots, inserts, narration, and continuity.
    - Gun in his Hand (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Written by Steven Fisher. First draft continuity 1/13/56.
    - In Times like These (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Written by Harry Segall. Revised first draft continuity 1/4/56, Bound with continuity breakdown.
    - Late George Apley (The) (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Adaption by Edward Hope. Revised shooting final 10/4/55.
    - Laura (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Adapted by Mel Dinelli. First draft 9/8/55.
    - Mama's Boarding House (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Written by Dorothy Cooper. First draft continuity 4/12/56.
    - Man of the Law (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Written by Daivd Lang. Final draft 12/10/56.
    - Man on the Ledge (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Written by Steve Fisher. Final draft 11/7/55.
    - Men Against Speed (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Written by John Robinson. First draft 7/26/56.
    - Miracle on 34th Street (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Adaption by John Monks Jr. Second draft 9/16/55, with wardrobe breakdown.
    - Money Maker (The) (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Shooting final,advance shooting schedule, staff, crew, cast lists, call sheets, production list, extra talent, requisition for extras.
    - Money Maker (The) (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Production materials, shooting final script, revised advanced shooting schedule, staff and crew list, casting vouchers, call sheets, extra talent, atmosphere budget, req. for extras
    - Money Maker (The) (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Adapted by Charles O'Neal. First draft Continuity, 6/12/56, Final shooting script 06/1/8/56.
    - Operation Cicero (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Written by Ben Feiner Jr. Unrevised final 8/3/56, Shooting final 8/10/56.
    - Overnight Haul (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Written by Leonard Freeman. Final draft 3/15/56, Shooting final 3/20/56.
    - Ox-Bow Incident (The) (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Written by David Dortort. Final script 6/28/55, with shooting schedule, cast list, staff list, casting vouchers for extra talent, daily production reports, call sheets.
    - Program #1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Written by Joe Parker and Henry Taylor. First draft 7/30/55.
    - Seven Steps (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Written by Kitty Buhler. Second draft 9/20/56.
    - Smoke Jumpers (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Written by Clark E. Reynolds. First draft Continuity 7/9/56, Final draft 7/17/56 with revised pages insertions.
    - Top Gun (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Written by Sam Peckinpah. First draft 7/27/56.
    - Window on the Sea (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Written by DeWitt Bodeen. First draft continuity 5/28/56, bound with production reports.
    - World of Emil Markeim (The) (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Written by Maurice Zimm. Shooting final 7/31/56, Revised shooting final 8/3/56.
    - Yacht on the High Sea (Box 15, Folder 17)
      Written by Whitfield Cook. Final draft 11/24/55.
    - Young Mr. Lincoln (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Staff, crew and cast list.
    - Young Mr. Lincoln (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Written by Maurice Zimm. First draft 9/7/56.
  - Affairs of China Smith (The)
    - Bible of Mr. Quaile (The) (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Written by Herb Purdum, with breakdown.
    - Devil Chaser (The) (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Written by Robert C. Dennis.
    - Escort to Saigon (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Manchu (The) (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Written by Geoffrey Homes.
    - Night the Dragon Walked (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Written by Robert C. Dennis, with cast list.
    - Plane to Tainan (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Written by Frank Burt. Second copy revised by Wilton Schiller, and Jack Laird.
    - Proverb of Shen-tze (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Written by Robert C. Dennis, with breakdown.
    - Sign of the Scorpion (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Talons of Tonking (The) (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Written by Lawrence Goldman, Wilton Schiller and Jack Laird.
    - Tidewalker (The) (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Written by Robert C. Dennis, with list with pencil revisions.
    - Traveller from Tsingtao (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Written by Robert C. Dennis, with Cast list.
    - Yellow Jade Lion (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Written by Rik Vollaerts and Lawrence Goldman, with cast list.
  - Best of the Post
    - Marriage that Couldn't Succeed (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Written by George Lefferts. Final shooting script, 12/5/56.
  - Broken Arrow
    - Apache Dowry (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Written by David T. Chantler. Final draft 10/26/56, with casting voucher, call sheets, shooting schedule, staff and crew list.
    - Attack on Fort Grant (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Written by Kay Lenard and Jess Carneol. First draft continuity 11/15/56.
    - Caged written by Warren Wilson (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Written by Warren Wilson. Final draft, 8/21/56, First draft 8/17/56.
    - Challenge written by Wallace Bosco (The) (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Written by Wallace Bosco. First draft, 8/21/56, Final draft 10/18/56, with cast list, salary scales, call sheets, staff and crew list.
    - Doctor (The) (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Written by Kay Lenard and Jess Carneol. Final draft 10/25/56, with staff and crew list, casting list call sheets, casting vouchers.
    - Ghostface (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Final draft 11/26/56, with cast lists, salary scale, revised shooting schedule, call sheets, staff and crew list.
    - Hermano (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Written by John Dunkel. Final draft 8/30/56, with combined master shooting schedule and one-line breakdown, call sheets, cast list.
    - Johnny Flagstaff (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Written by Warren Wilson. First draft continuity 11/29/56.
    - Legacy of a Hero (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Written by Wilton Schiller. Final draft 11/12/56, Incl. crew and cast list, call sheets, shooting schedule, list of added shots.
    - Mail Riders (The) (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Written by Clark E. Reynolds. First draft continuity 8/6/56, Final script 8/13/56, Final master shooting schedule, with cast list, days-out-of-days cast schedule, one page re- write.
    - Mirage (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Written by Warren Wilson. Final draft 9/7/56, with cast lists, call sheets. (new title Cry Wolf).
    - Missionaries (The) (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Written by Dave Victor and Herbert Little. Final script 10/23/56, with cast lists call sheets, casting voucher.
    - Passage Deferred (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Written by Jan Leman and Ted Thomas. Final script 8/3/56, with music clearance, cast lists, day-out-of-days cast schedule, extra talent and stuntmen budget, horses and wranglers.
    - Powder Keg (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Written by Arthur Orloff. Final script 10/18/56.Incl. cast lists, staff and crew list, combined shooting schedule and one line breakdown, call sheets.
    - Pursued (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Written by Rik Vollaerts. Final draft 10/1/56, Revised final 10/15/56.
    - Raiders (The) (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Written by William Leicester. First Draft 8/17/56, Final script 8/20/56, Incl. cast lists, day-out-of-days cast schedule, master shooting schedule, call sheets.
    - Rebellion (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Written by DeVallon Scott. Final draft, 11/20/56, with cast lists, staff and crew list call sheets.
    - Return from the Shadows (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Written by William R. Cox. First draft 9/14/56, with cast lists, staff and crew list, call sheets.
    - San Francisco (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Written by Harold Swanton. New title Indian Bureau Scandal, First draft continuity 8/28/56, Final script 9/10/56, Master shooting schedule, with cast lists, call sheets.
  - Millionaire
    - Luke Fortune (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Written by Mary C. McCall, Jr. Revised script 2/24/56.
  - My Friend Flicka
    - Camera Man (The) (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Written by Jan Lehman, Ted Thomas and Lowell S. Hawley, Shooting final 3/13/56.
    - Lock, Stock and Barrel (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Written by Warren Wilson. Shooting final 5/25/56.
    - Lost River (The) (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Written by Jerry Sackheim. Final draft 12/5/55.
    - Old Danny (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Shooting final 3/15/56.
    - Phantome Herd (The) (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Written by Peter Packer. Shooting final 5/9/55.
    - Rouge Stallion (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Final script 8/1/55.
    - Runaways (The) (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Written by Kay Lenard. Shooting final 3/9/56.
    - Unmasking (The) (Box 15, Folder 8)
      Written by David Lang. Shooting final 6/11/56.
    - Wind from Heaven (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Written by George Asness. Final script 12/2/55.
  - Sheriff of Cochise
    - Medal of Honor (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Written by David Robinson.
  - You Are There
    - Courage of Stephen Decatur (The) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Cut Charlie In (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Cast sheet.
    - Daniel Webster's Sacrifice to Save the Union (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - End of the Dalton Gang (The) (Box 15, Folder 14)
      Written by Jack Bennett. 6/18/56.
    - Fall of Fort Sumter (The) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Fall Of Fort Sumter (The) (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Production materials: script, call sheet, breakdown, cast list with salary, staff and crew list, extra cost schedule, casting voucher and production reports.
    - First Moscow Purge Trial (The) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - First Moscow Purge Trial (The) (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Production materials: scripts, call sheets, breakdown, bit and cast lists, extras cost schedule, cast list with salary, staff and crew list.
    - Great Diamond Fraud (The) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Great Diamond Fraud (The) (Box 19, Folder 1)